I'm getting my nails done!
我居然在修指甲
You said it was going to be fun.
你說會很好玩
Which it kind of is.
是有點好玩
You said there would be guys. There are no guys.
你說會有別的男人，哪有啊
There's one right over there.
那邊就有一個
That's a mailman!
那是快遞
That's our mailman!
他也跑我們公司
Hi,how are you....
Don't worry. This doesn't make you any less of a guy.
放心 這樣無損於你的男子氣概
That does.
那樣會
What am I sitting on?
我坐到什麼？
What was this woman scratching when this broke off?
這個女人不知道在搔哪裡
You know who had nails like that?
你知道誰也戴那種指甲？
Oh...
我…
...my...
的…
...God!
天哪！
The One with All the Rugby
本集播出：「調職記」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Joey,let me ask you a question.
喬伊，問你一個問題
What does this light switch do?
我快捉狂了 這個開關是幹嘛用的？
Nothing.
沒用
Did it drive you crazy to not know?
你不知道不會捉狂嗎？
I know what it did. Nothing.
我知道啊. 它沒用
They put it there for something. How can you not care?
它存在就一定有功用 你怎麼能不在意？
Like this.
就像這樣
Here's another question.
還有一個問題
What does the silver knob on the toilet do?
你知道馬桶上的把手的功用嗎
It flushes it.
當然知道，沖水
Since you know,when you come over, would you use it?
很好，既然你知道，來的時候 請你沖一下好嗎？
-Hello. -Hey.
-Oh,my God. Wow. -Guess who we saw today?
猜我們今天遇見誰
-Janice! -ls this amazing?
珍妮絲 很棒吧？
-How have you been? -Well,I'm divorced.
你好嗎？ 我離婚了
Oh,wow.
I'm riding the alimony pony.
正在靠贍養費過活
And there it is.
出現了
I just came up to say "hi."
我只是來打聲招呼，大家好
Sweetie,I'll see you later.
親愛的，我們待會見
I'll see you tonight.
晚上見
-Bye. -Bye.
再見，再見…
I can't stand the woman!
我受不了那個女人
What? I thought you were crazy about her!
什麼？我以為你愛死她了
But you know all those annoying things she did before?
我知道 但是以前她那些很煩的特點
Her voice,her laugh and her personality?
她的聲音、笑聲和個性
They're all back!
全都回來了
And she's picked up,like, nine new ones!
而且還多了起碼九種新的
Why'd you bring her here? There's people here!
那你幹嘛帶她來？虐待人嘛
Don't worry. I'm taking care of it.
放心，我今晚會搞定
You are not! You never break up with her.
會才怪，你一直跟她糾纏不清
I don't have to break up.
這次我不必跟她分手
We're not involved. I'll do a preemptive strike.
我們又沒在一起 我會先發制人
I'll end it with her before it starts.
我會在開始前就結束掉
My ass is,like,frozen!
我的屁股好冰
Try sticking it in the freezer for 20 minutes.
塞進冷凍庫20分鐘試試看
I'm telling you!
不要不信
I can't believe you walk alone here at night.
你居然敢晚上自己走在路上
-You hear such stories about New York. -It's not that bad.
紐約的傳聞好多 沒那麼嚴重
I mean,l,for one, feel perfectly safe.
我就覺得很安全
Help! Help!
救命啊！救命啊！
No,no,Ross!
羅斯，沒事
These are friends from home.
他們是我在英國的朋友
Liam,Devon,this is Ross.
連恩，戴文，這是羅斯
-Hi,mate. -How are you,man?
老兄 你們好
That was a good one,huh? "Help! Help!"
我裝得不錯吧？ 「救命啊！救命啊」
How are you?
你們好嗎？
I've been meaning to ring you ever since I arrived...
我從一來就想找你們
...but I've been rather busy.
但是…我挺忙的
We have not seen each other since that U2 concert.
我們從U2演唱會之後 就沒見過
Oh,my God. You're right.
天哪，沒錯
Actually,the last time we saw each other was the next morning.
應該說是演唱會第二天早上
Oh,Liam!
連恩
Oh,Liam.
So were you guys playing soccer?
你們在打足球？
Or should I call it "football"?
還是要說「踢」足球？
We were playing rugby.
我們在打橄欖球
In fact,we're playing tomorrow. You're welcome to play.
明天就有球賽，歡迎你參加
Ross play rugby? I don't think so.
羅斯打橄欖球？不要吧
What's so funny?
有什麼可笑的？
Well,you're American,to start with. You don't have rugby here.
你是美國人 美國沒有橄欖球
Well,we didn't have freedom here until 1776 either,so....
我們也是到了1776年 才獨立自由
So,good! We'll see you at the park at two.
那好，明天2點公園見
Cheers!
乾杯
Oh,boy! I just love to sing.
天哪，我最喜歡唱歌了
Yes,I know you do.
我知道你喜歡
The reason people complained...
其他人之所以抱怨
...was because they paid to hear the actor sing "Old Man River."
是因為他們是花錢聽演員唱
Look at us!
你看看我們
Who would've thought Cupid had a station at 14th Street Nails?
想不到在美容院也有愛神駐紮
Okay,we have to talk.
我們得談一談
I'm just getting out of a very serious relationship.
我剛結束一段很認真的戀情
I know. And I'm just getting out of a marriage.
我知道，而我剛結束一段婚姻
Talk about "meant to be."
這就叫做三生注定
Right. But I think this is happening too soon.
對，但我覺得進展太快了
Oh,too soon,too schmoon!
什麼太快，是太慢
Face it,I'm not letting you get away this time.
認命吧，這次我不會放過你的
I hear you!
我聽見了
But...
但是
...unfortunately...
很不幸的
...my company...
我的公司
...is transferring me overseas.
要把我調到海外
Oh,no!
不會吧
Where to?
調去哪裡？
To Paris?
巴黎？
No,not Paris.
不，不是巴黎
To London? Rome? Vienna?
倫敦？羅馬？維也納？
Barcelona?
巴塞隆納？
Could you just stop talking for a second?
你先別講話好嗎？
Yemen.
葉門
That's right. Yes! I'm being transferred to Yemen!
對，沒錯，我要被調去葉門
When?
什麼時候？
I don't know exactly.
我不太清楚
Well,I will just have to soak up every ounce...
那我只好細細品嚐
...of Chandler Bing until that moment comes.
錢德賓的一切 直到那一刻來臨
But I do know it's sometime tomorrow.
但我知道是明天某時
-Done? -Yep!
好了？ 對
What's up?
幹什麼？
This switch is driving me crazy.
這個開關快把我逼瘋了
I turned it off and checked every outlet.
所以我把它關掉 檢查每個插座
Four don't work,which means one is controlled by the switch.
有四個不能用 表示其中一個由它控制
So I plugged things in the outlets that make noise.
所以我插上會發出聲音的東西
That way,when I turn it on, I just follow the noise.
到時候一打開 順著聲音去找就行了
Bet I stopped listening first.
我一定會第一個放棄
You know,you also could have used lamps...
你可以插電燈
...and followed the light.
然後找燈光
Yeah,well,I'm using noise.
我要找聲音
So,everybody ready?
準備好了嗎？
Here we go!
開咯
Something. I hear something. Where is it?
有聲音，我聽到了，在哪裡？
It's coming from Joey!
是喬伊發出來的
Oh,my God! That's so freaky! Turn him off!
天哪，好詭異喔，把他關掉！
Could we put on the news? It might be raining.
可以看新聞嗎？可能在下雨
Hold on. I'm watching this rugby thing on ESPN.
等一下 我在看ESPN的橄欖球賽
I'm man enough to play this sport!
了不起啊，我也能打
You're not even man enough to get the channel that carries the sport.
你家連運動台都沒有
Hey there,Ross!
羅斯
Janice.
是珍妮絲
You know,you really didn't have to help me pack.
你真的不必幫我打包
When you said all you'd be doing before you leave is packing...
你說你出發之前都要打包
...you really didn't leave me much choice.
我還有什麼選擇
I thought I did, but I guess I did not.
我以為有，看來是沒有
What's going on?
怎麼回事？
I'm packing,you know, because I'm moving to Yemen tomorrow.
我要打包 因為我明天要搬去葉門
Thanks for telling me!
謝謝你告訴我啊
I'm going to be pretend-moving to Yemen. To get rid of her.
我是假裝要搬去葉門 好擺脫她
Good one!
漂亮
Yemen! That actually sounds like a real country!
葉門，聽起來還真像個國家
I'll show you how to roll your underwear and stuff it in your shoes.
錢德，快來 我教你怎麼把內衣褲塞進鞋子
It's a space-saver.
可以省空間
I do that because it makes me look taller.
我那樣做是想墊高
Come on!
錢德，來啊 好
-Joey,trade lives with me. -Nope.
喬伊，跟我交換人生 不要
Ross,I can't believe you said you'd play.
天哪，你看看 羅斯，你居然說你要打
This is brutal!
這種運動好野蠻
I can handle it.
我可以應付
Please,Ross. You got hurt playing badminton with my dad.
拜託 你連跟我爸打羽毛球都會受傷
That's because your mom's dog kept looking at me.
那是因為你媽的狗一直看我
Look! Right here, it's called a "scrum."
好，你看，這個叫鬥牛陣
It's like a huddle.
就像聚商
And is a hum like a scruddle?
那商斗就像聚牛陣嗎？
Ross,they're going kill you!
羅斯，他們會宰了你
Why are you doing this,anyway?
你為什麼要打？
You should've seen the guy she used to date.
你們應該看看她以前交往的人
He's like "Joe Rugby"!
他活像顆大橄欖球
You're kidding! And he plays rugby? That's funny!
不會吧，而他又打橄欖球？ 好好玩
Oh,I see. You did that.
我懂你的意思了
She thought the very idea of me playing rugby was hilarious.
總之她覺得我打橄欖球很好笑
So I'll show her how tough I really am.
所以我要證明我有多猛
I'm sorry. You are a tough guy.
對不起，你說得對，你是很猛
The toughest paleontologist I know.
你是我認識最猛的古生物學家
Ross can take care of himself. It's not like he's Chandler.
沒問題啦，羅斯會照顧自己 他又不是錢德
Thanks.
謝了
Don't worry about me.
別替我擔心
I'll just look energetic and stay away from the ball.
我會裝得很有衝勁 跟球保持距離
I'll be that guy, right outside the circle.
我會學那個人站在外面
Maybe there was a dog looking at him.
也許有狗在看他
Stay away from that guy and that guy...
羅斯，別靠近那個人、那個人
...and that one. Dude,they're all huge!
和那個人 他們都好壯
They're no bigger than me.
又沒比我壯
You're closer to you. So you look bigger to you from where you are.
你離你比較近 所以看你自己比較壯
I'm going to go say "hello."
我去跟他們打個招呼
I kind of liked it.
還蠻可愛的
I know what to do.
我知道了
I've got to go Red Ross.
我要變成赤面羅斯
You know,Red Ross?
赤面羅斯啊
Totally don't know.
完全給他不知道
That time we were in line for Dances With Wolves...
那次我們去看「與狼共舞」
...and that guy cut in front of us and I just lost it?
有人插隊，我不是就捉狂了？
Screamed at him,turned all red!
破口大罵，臉都漲紅了
Red Ross!
赤面羅斯啊
You'll see!
等著瞧
Liam,do me a favor.
連恩，幫個忙
Go easy on Ross. It's his first time.
對羅斯手下留情 他是第一次打
You don't say?
是嗎？
Good luck,babe.
加油
Come on,get in here!
老弟，快進來
Come on!
快點
Come on,get in the bloody scrum!
羅斯，快進來爭球
Ross,get in!
羅斯，進去
Joey!
喬伊
You're not going to believe it! Joshua came in today,and guess what?
說了你一定不信 約書亞今天來，你猜怎樣？
He asked you out?
他約你？ 沒有
But I showed him some cuff links, and I felt his pulse.
不過我給他看一些袖扣 結果摸到他的脈搏
Saucy!
卯死了
-What are these? -Electrical plans for the building.
這是什麼？ 這棟樓的電路圖
Okay,should I be scared?
我應該被嚇到嗎？
I know that switch does something. I got these from City Hall.
那個開關一定有作用 這是去市政府調的
I just paid $25 and waited for three hours.
只花了25元，排了3小時
Wow! If only more people knew!
可惜大家不知道
All right,do you understand any of this?
你看得懂嗎？
No,I don't understand any of this electrical stuff.
我對水電的事一竅不通
All right,does this look like a switch?
這看起來像開關嗎？
I don't know.
我不知道
-ls this wiring? -I don't know.
這是線路嗎？ 我不知道
That looks like a bunny though.
不過這個像小白兔
「葉門航空」
You really didn't have to take me to the airport.
你實在不必送我來機場
Oh,please. Every moment is precious.
拜託，每分每秒都很珍貴
Besides,someone had to ride with your luggage.
況且總得有人幫你提行李
And your friends don't seem to care that you're leaving.
你朋友好像都不關心你要走了
We're not that close.
我們其實沒那麼要好
Okay. So I guess this is goodbye then.
好，那就再見了
Oh,no!
不
It's not goodbye. I'm not leaving till you get on that plane.
還沒呢 你上了飛機我才要走
Okay. Well,I guess it's just "wait here" then.
好，那就「請在此等候」
I need a fake ticket to Yemen.
我要一張去葉門的假機票
One ticket?
一張去葉門的機票？ 不是
I just need a pretend ticket.
我只需要一張假機票
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
抱歉，我不懂
Okay,what would you give a kid to play with?
好，你會拿什麼給小朋友玩？
Are you traveling with a child?
您有帶小孩子？
No.
沒有
She'll think I'm handing you a credit card.
她會以為我在拿信用卡給你
But what I'll really hand you is a library card.
其實我拿的是借書證
A ticket to Yemen is $2100, and we don't take library cards.
去葉門的機票是2100元 我們不收借書證
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
怎麼了？有什麼問題嗎？
Do you have to stay?
你得留下來嗎？
American Express?
美國運通卡？
I can't believe they're doing that! I told them to go easy on him!
他們怎麼這樣 我明明叫他們手下留情
No offense,but sometimes it's hard to understand you,with the accent.
我沒有惡意 但有時你的口音很難懂
That's just halftime. There's more.
才上半場結束，還有下半場
Did you see me?
你們看到了嗎？
I was pretty good. That is one fun game!
我挺強的 好過癮的球賽
Do me a favor? Grab me some water?
幫個忙，幫我拿點水
Thanks!
謝謝
I think I'm dying. I really do.
我覺得我快死了，真的
Poor baby!
真可憐
Tell my son that I love him.
告訴我兒子我愛他
Excellent! Got to have some more fun!
太好了，我還要再打個過癮
They are killing you.
羅斯，你快被整死了
That's not true.
亂講
She's right. You have to stop!
她說得對，你不能再打了
No! I'm not stopping. I'm Red Ross!
不行，我是赤面羅斯
Dude,you go back out there, you'll be Dead Ross.
你再上場會變成屎面羅斯
I'm not quitting. I'm going to finish this game.
我絕不退場，我要打完
If you insist on it, at least let me help you.
好，如果你一定要打 至少讓我幫忙
It's no place for a woman. Those guys will grab anything!
不行，這不是女人玩的 那些人什麼都捉
That's not it. I just know a few things that can help you inflict pain.
我不是要上場 我只是知道怎樣讓別人受傷
I like that.
我喜歡 是嗎？
Listen closely.
聽好
Devon has got a weak ankle.
戴文的腳踝很弱
One swift kick and he'll back off.
踢一下就會倒
Bad ankle. Got it!
好，腳踝虛，瞭解
And that big bloke with the beard? He's got a trick hip.
那個留落腮鬍的大個子 腰部毛病很多
And David over there, he doesn't wear a cup.
那邊的大衛沒穿護襠
I could use that. Trick hip,no cup. Okay!
蠻有用的，腰不好 沒穿護襠，好
And Liam's got bad knees. Hit him right and he'll go down like a lamp.
連恩的膝蓋不好 看準了一撞就倒
But Liam's on my team.
但是連恩跟我同隊
-I don't care. Just get him! -Go and get him!
我不管，你去宰了他 好，宰了他
I am going back in!
我要回場上了
Red Ross! Yeah!
赤面羅斯
What are these?
這些是什麼？
Just some pictures I made and hung up.
我畫了一些畫掛起來
I thought they'd brighten up the place. Don't they?
好讓客廳看起來更漂亮 有用吧？
No,don't.
There's no hole there. I just really like that picture.
那裡沒有洞 我只是很喜歡那幅畫
Oh,my God! Look at this!
天哪，你看看
But there is a wire there! It's connected to something!
但是那邊有電線 一定連到某個地方
I don't care! The wires have come loose in your head!
我不管，你才是腦筋脫線了
If I could follow the wire, I'd find out what it did.
順著電線就能找出它的功用
And did you?
那你找到了嗎？
No.
沒有
It disappears behind there.
到了地板上就斷了
For a minute,I thought it went downstairs.
Say hello to Mrs. Catrokis.
跟凱卓奇斯太太打招呼
-Hello,darling. -Hello,Mrs. Catrokis.
妹妹你好 凱卓奇斯太太你好
Hey,Mrs. Catrokis,do you know Kenny?
凱卓奇斯太太，你認識肯尼嗎
You have got to be kid Wow!
不會吧
Are you sure you don't want a doctor?
你真的不去看醫生？
No,that'll just bring me down!
不要，那樣我會直接掛掉
This was great! I was great! This was a great day!
太棒了 我太厲害了，今天真過癮
I'm buying everyone coffee.
我請大家喝咖啡
Just grab my wallet. It's in my pocket.
幫我拿皮夾，在我的口袋裡
No,not you.
不是你
Your eye's still popping out. I'll go get some ice.
你的眼睛還是突的 我去拿冰塊
Ice,yeah! I'm so in the mood for ice.
好 冰塊，我正想吃冰塊
You were amazing out there.
你剛才好神勇
I kind of was,wasn't l?
還蠻神勇的吧？ 開玩笑
Oh,my God!
I made a man twice my size cry!
我讓一個壯我兩倍的人哭了
I haven't done that since I was four and I washed my dad's Porsche with rocks.
上一次是4歲 我用石頭洗我爸的保時捷
You really enjoyed yourself, didn't you?
你真的打得很過癮對不對？
Are you kidding? I hurt three huge men.
開玩笑，我幹掉三個大塊頭
I gave a guy a bloody nose!
還讓一個人流鼻血
I'm not proud of it...
這沒什麼好得意的
...but I really am!
不過…我真的好得意
And it's all because of you.
都是因為你
-Wonderful,amazing you. -I think you've got a concussion.
最棒最棒的你 我看你是腦震盪了
No,I'm serious. Thank you.
不，我是說真的，謝謝你
You're welcome.
不客氣
I'm sorry. Did that hurt you?
對不起，會痛嗎？
It's worth the pain.
痛也值得
You know what? It's not.
其實不值得
This is the final boarding call for flight 664 to Yemen.
最後一次呼叫前往葉門的旅客
Well,I guess I gotta go.
看來我該走了
My Bing-a-ling.
我的賓淇淋
I'll wait for you.
我會等你的
How long will you be gone?
你要去多久？
Well,just until we find an energy source to replace fuel.
直到找出可以替代石油的能源
I'll write you every day.
我會每天寫信給你
15 Yemen Road,Yemen.
葉門葉門路15號
Okay. Goodbye.
好，再見
錢德，錢德
Janice! There you are! I had to have one last kiss.
珍妮絲，你在這裡 我得跟你做最後吻別
And also,you said you'd leave after I got on the plane!
另外你也說我一上機你就要走
No. I want to see you take off.
不，我想看著你起飛
Well,then I guess I'm going to Yemen.
那我要去葉門羅
I'm going to Yemen!
我要去葉門了
When we get to Yemen, can I stay with you?
到了葉門，我可以住你家嗎？
All right. The super couldn't figure out what it did.
好，管理員不知道它的作用
The $200-an-hour electrician couldn't figure out what it did.
1小時2百的電工 不曉得它的作用
I've had seven pretty serious shocks.
我被狠狠電到七次
I give up.
我放棄了
Thank God.
謝天謝地
I guess Joey was right.
看來喬伊說得對
It does nothing.
它沒有用
See?
你看
I'm doing it! I am totally doing it!
是我弄的，真的是我弄的
I lost it.
超能力沒了